<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, PrinterHack!</string>
    <string name="app_name">PrinterHack</string>
    <string name="help_title">PrinterHack Help</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="about_title">PrinterHack About</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="donate_title">Help me pay for college</string>
    <string name="donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="rdymsg_help_text">RDYMSG commands, or ready message commands, 
    	are used to change a printer\'s \'ready\' message. 
    	\n\nThis has many entertaining possibilities - I recommend 
    	trying things like \'insert coin\' or \'out of cheese\'.</string>
   	<string name="opmsg_help_text">OPMSG commands, or operator message commands,
      	are intended to display a message on the printer which 
   		can be canceled by pressing the printer\'s \'ok\' button. 
   		\nThese commands will behave differently on different models - 
   		possible behaviors include beeping, pausing printing, or flashing a light 
   		when an OPMSG is received.</string>
  	<string name="app_help_text"><b>Overview:</b>
  		\nThis application is designed to be able to use a standard called PJL, or 
  		Printer Job Language, to change the ready message on certain types of printers. It is also capable of 
  		sending commands which will cause printers to display an \'operator message\' to the user. 
  		\nThe primary use for this program is probably pranking, but it certaintly has the potential for 
  		other, more legitimate uses as well.
  		\n
  		\n<b>How to use:</b>
  		\nTo use this program, you need to do two things:
  		\n- Figure out the IP of the network printer you wish to hack
  		\n- Connect to a wifi network where the printer is accessible
  		\nOnce you\'ve got that taken care of, simply open the program, input your message, and 
  		click one of the two commands below the message box.
  		\n
  		\n<b>How to find your printer\'s IP:</b>
  		\nThere are two ways to find the IP of your network printer. The first is to print a network report 
  		using the printer\'s menu. Most printers which support PJL will have this option under 
  		\'reports\' or \'status\'. The second way is to find the IP by looking up the printer on a 
  		computer which is already connected to the printer. You can find instructions for how to do this at http://www.findmyip.org/find-network-printer-ip.php
  		</string>
	
	<string name="app_about_text"><b>About Printerhack:</b>
		\nPrinterhack is written by Quinn Rohlf and the core printer code is licensed under the Apache 2.0 open source license. 
		You can view the source at http://qrohlf.com. The program was originally developed just for my own amusement, 
		and after a friend found it and played around with it at school, I realized that there was probably a market 
		for this sort of thing. The version you\'re using is a much more polished version than the original, and was 
		written with the intent of making a little bit of money for college. 
		\n
		\nActually, money for college is one of the main goals I have with Android development, so it would be really 
		cool of you to donate via my <a href="http://qrohlf.com/donate/">website</a>!
	</string>
	<string name="app_donate_text">
		Hi, I\'m an 18 year old student who does Android development in his spare time. If you found this app helpful or useful,
		it would be really rad if you would donate to me, either by buying the donate version of this app in the Market, or by donating 
		via the paypal button on my <a href="http://qrohlf.com/donate/">website</a>. If you do, I\'ll probably send you a postcard or a beta version of one of my apps.
		\n
		\nCheers,
		\n-QRohlf
	</string>
</resources>
